Usage: corpus [OPTIONS] COMMAND [ARGS]...

  CorpusRAG ù unified learning and knowledge management toolkit.

  Run any subcommand with --help for details.

Options:
  --version  Show the version and exit.
  --help     Show this message and exit.

Commands:
  benchmark    Run performance benchmarks on a collection.
  setup        Run interactive setup wizard for first-time configuration.
  collections  Manage vector database collections.
  db           Database management commands.
  dev          Developer utilities (setup, test, lint, build, clean,...
  flashcards   Generate flashcards from a collection.
  handwriting
  orchestrate  Orchestration workflows for Corpus Callosum.
  quizzes      Generate quiz questions from a collection.
  rag          RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) tool.
  summaries    Generate summary from a collection.
  video        Video transcription and processing tool.
